logler.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Game Downloads at Logler.com

[Download Games](http://www.logler.com/) > Privacy Policy

Logler Games Privacy Policy: Updated June 15, 2007

Please read this document carefully before accessing the content on this web site.

Logler respects your right to privacy. We understand the sensitive nature of privacy issues and we take appropriate actions to ensure that your confidentiality is protected. Logler provides this privacy policy to inform you of our web site practices with respect to the way your information is collected and used.

**Information Collection and Use**

Logler is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Logler may sell or transfer Personal Information to third parties in connection with any merger, acquisition, reorganization, change in capital structure, sale of all or substantially all of its assets. When purchasing games from us, or from one of our ecommerce partners, your Personal Information is encrypted. We do not store your complete credit card information for your personal protection. We may transfer Personal Information to third parties, who are under contract, as necessary to provide a product or service that an individual purchased or ordered from Logler. Logler collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing anonymous information about the user. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Logler is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter we ask for contact information such as name and email address. This information will be used only for the purposes of our newsletter and will not be shared with any outside parties. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving it by clicking on the link to do so in the body of the email. 

**Purchases**

If you make a purchase from us through our site, we will ask you to provide certain information, including your contact details (such as your name, address, telephone and email), and your billing information (such as your credit card number and the date that your card expires). We will use this information to process your transaction and to contact you regarding your purchase if necessary. We will share this information with our payment processor to the extent necessary to facilitate your purchase (for purposes such as customer service, verification, fulfillment and billing purposes). We will not sell or rent your personal billing information to any third party. 

**Referral Service**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about a game listed within our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Logler will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Logler does not store this information. 

By using the web site, you signify your understanding of our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the web site. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or any other privacy issues in connection with the web site, please submit your inquiry using our contact form within the site.

**THIS POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME, SO PLEASE CHECK BACK FOR UPDATES OR CHANGES**.

Thank you for your attention. Enjoy our games!
